<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CWTSato</string>
    <string name="logo">CWTSato To Go</string>
    <string name="sato_sign_in_active_not_verified_txt"><Data><![CDATA[<b>Thank you for creating your CWTSato To Go Account.</b><br><br>Please follow directions found in an email that has been sent to your registered address to verify your account.<br><br>If you don’t receive the email, please check your spam or junk mail filter or: <br><br><a href="">Click here to resend</a> ]]></Data></string>
	<string name="sato_sign_in_active_not_verified_bottom_txt"><Data><![CDATA[<br>Did you already verify your account? <a href="">Click here to sign in.</a> ]]></Data></string>
	<string name="sato_sign_in_terms_of_use">By signing in you agree to our <a href="">Terms of Use</a></string>
	<string name="about_version_format">CWTSato To Go v.%s</string>
	<string name="flight_reminder_buttons_details">Open CWTSato To Go</string>
	<string name="flight_alert_notification_ticker">CWTSato To Go: Flight alert</string>
    <string name="notification_common_title_with_prefix_format">CWTSato To Go: %1$s</string>
	<string name="itinerary_change_notification_ticker_text">CWTSato To Go: Itinerary updated</string>
	<string name="rate_us_dialog_button_rate">Rate CWTSato To Go</string>
	<string name="rate_us_dialog_message_format">Love CWTSato To Go? Give us a 5\u00A0star rating on %1$s</string>
	<string name="enter_cwt_office_number_to_book">Enter CWTSatoTravel office number to book</string>
	<string name="settings_notification_flight_alert_play_test_flight_alert_message_prefix">CWT Sato To Go:</string>
	
	<!-- strings with changed email -->
	<string name="morning_assistant_upcoming_trips_none_address">plans@cwtsatotogo.com</string>
	<string name="empty_trip_line1">You can add flights, hotels, rental cars and more by forwarding your confirmation emails to: plans@cwtsatotogo.com.</string>
	<string name="empty_upcoming_trips_line1">Your CWTSatoTravel trips automatically display within CWTSato To Go. Please allow up to 30 minutes.</string>
	<string name="empty_upcoming_trips_line2">Have a reservation that wasn\'t made with CWTSatoTravel? Simply forward the confirmation email to plans@cwtsatotogo.com</string>
	<string name="widget_description_long">Your CWTSatoTravel trips automatically display within CWTSato To Go.  Have a reservation that wasn\'t made with CWTSatoTravel? Simply forward the confirmation email to plans@cwtsatotogo.com</string>
	<string name="general_footer_text_email_link">plans@cwtsatotogo.com</string>
	<string name="forward_email_address">plans@cwtsatotogo.com</string>


	<string name="settings_edit_phone">My Local CWTSatoTravel Office</string>
	<string name="terms_of_use_link">http://www.cwtsatotogo.com/mobile/terms_of_use.php?lang=en</string>

	<string name="settings_contact_cwt_agent_title">Contact CWTSatoTravel</string>

    <string name="cwt_wellcome_screen_pager_des_page2">Trips booked through CWTSatoTravel are automatically displayed while a simple email to plans@cwtsatotogo.com will integrate trips you have made through other channels.</string>
    <string name="cwt_wellcome_screen_pager_des_page3">CWTSato To Go keeps you  informed of delays, cancellations, gate assignments and changes so that you can proactively stay on track.</string>
	
    <!-- strings for login screen -->
    <string name="signin_forgot_password"><a href="">Forgot/change password?</a></string>
    <string name="switch_user_button_login"><Data><![CDATA[Or <a href="">Sign in</a> with a different account]]></Data></string>
    <string name="logout_before_login_with_new_user">To log-in to a different account, please click the \'Sign in with a different account\' button</string>
    <string name="lock_screen_message">You have been logged out. Please enter your user name and password:</string>
    <string name="approved_by_goverment">CWTSato To Go is approved by the US government</string>
    <string name="warning_title">WARNING</string>
    <string name="warning_message">Privacy Act Notice\nWARNING MESSAGE\nCWTSato To Go is an application being provided to our customers as a convenience. It is not necessary to use this application to obtain travel services from us.  However these systems and equipment are subject to monitoring by us as part of our security procedures.  Users shall not access other user\' or system files without proper authority. Absence of access controls IS NOT authorization for access! Monitoring may result in the acquisition, recording, and analysis of all data being communicated, transmitted, processed, or stored in this system by authorized officials. Use of this system constitutes consent to such monitoring.\nUnder some of our U.S. government contracts, the U.S. Government retains ownership of any data entered into information systems used in the performance of a government contract.  To the extent, the U.S. Government does not retain ownership of the information or data, then CW Government Travel, Inc. will hold ownership of any information you provide us. We will not sell ownership of this data to any other company or organization. We will not transfer information to competitors. If you are providing personal information within a registration page, it will only be used within our domain unless you choose to allow third party data sharing.\nYour Acceptance of these Terms\nBy using this site, you agree to our Privacy Policy. We may change the Policy from time to time, so please be sure to visit this section often to see if anything has changed. If we post changes and you continue to use the site, you will be deemed to have agreed to the changes.\nWhat Kind of Security Procedures are in Place to Protect the Loss, Misuse or Alteration of Information under the Company\'s Control?\nWe operate secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our customers. Any particularly sensitive information, such as a customer\'s credit card number, is encrypted prior to transmission. In accordance with the Privacy Act (5 U.S.C.552a), the following notice is provided:\nThis system may contain information protected under the provisions of the Privacy Act of 1974 (Public Law 93-579). Any privacy information displayed on the screen or printed must be protected from unauthorized disclosure. Employees who violate privacy safeguards may be subject to disciplinary actions, a fine of up to $5,000, or both.\nThe information requested is for the purpose of providing our military and government customers with online access to, among other things, flight notifications, including delays, cancellations and gate changes, real-time flight status integrated into your trip, check in with more than 250 airlines, the ability to search for alternative flight schedules.\nIf you are a CWTSatoTravel E2 Solutions customer under ETS2 or ETS1, there are some additional provisions that may apply.\nIf you are an E2 Solutions user, information is collected pursuant to Executive Order 9397 and Chapter 57, Title 5 United States Code for the purpose of recording travel information provided by the user to create travel itineraries, reserve any method or mode of travel accommodations, and claim entitlements and allowances prescribed in applicable Federal travel regulations. The purpose of the collection of this information is to establish a comprehensive travel services system which enables travel service providers under contract with the Federal Government to authorize, issue, and account for travel and travel reimbursements provided to individuals on official Federal Government business. Routine uses which may be made of the collected information and other financial account information in the system(s) of record entitled "Contracted Travel Services Program GSA/GOVT-4" are as follows: (1) transfers to a Federal, state, local, or foreign agency responsible for investigating, prosecuting, enforcing, or carrying out a statute, rule, regulation, or order, where agencies become aware of a violation or potential violation of civil or criminal law or regulation; (2) pursuant to a request of another Federal agency or a court when the Federal Government is party to a judicial proceeding; (3) to a Member of Congress or a congressional staff member in response to an inquiry from that congressional office made at the request of the individual who is the subject of the record; (4) to a Federal agency employee, expert, consultant, or contractor in performing a Federal duty for purposes of authorizing, arranging, and/or claiming reimbursement for official travel, including, but not limited to, traveler profile information; (5) to a credit card company for billing purposes, including collection of past due amounts; (6) to a Federal agency, expert, consultant, or contractor for accumulating reporting data, conducting surveys, and monitoring the system in the performance of a Federal duty; (7) to a Federal agency by the contractor in the form of itemized statements or invoices, and reports of all transactions, including refunds and adjustments to enable audits of charges to the Federal Government; (8) to a Federal agency, in response to its request, in connection with the hiring or retention of any employee to the extent that the information is relevant and necessary to the requesting agency\'s decision on the matter; (9) to an authorized appeal or grievance examiner, formal complaints examiner, equal employment opportunity investigator, arbitrator, or other duly authorized official engaged in investigation or settlement of a grievance, complaint, or appeal filed by an employee to whom the information pertains; (10) to the Office of Personnel Management (OPM) in accordance with the agency\'s responsibility for evaluation of Federal personnel management; (11) to officials of labor organizations recognized under 5 U.S.C. Chapter 71 when relevant and necessary to their duties of exclusive representation concerning personnel policies, practices, and matters affecting working conditions; (12) to a travel services provider for billing and refund purposes; (13) to a carrier or an insurer for settlement of an employee claim for loss of or damage to personal property incident to service under 31 U.S.C. § 3721, or to a party involved in a tort claim against the Federal Government resulting from an accident involving a traveler; (14) to a credit reporting agency or credit bureau, as allowed and authorized by law, for the purpose of adding to a credit history file when it has been determined that an individual\'s account with a creditor with input to the system is delinquent; (15) summary or statistical data from the system with no reference to an identifiable individual may be released publicly; and (16) any other use specified by GSA in the system of records entitled "Contracted Travel Services Program GSA/GOVT-4" as published in the Federal Register periodically by GSA.\nInformation requested is voluntary, however, failure to provide the information may prevent you from using the features of CWTSato To Go.\nBy clicking "Accept" you confirm that you have read and acknowledge the Warning Message and Privacy Act Notice.</string>
    <string name="password_policy">Password should be 8&#8211;24 characters long and include at least: one uppercase, one lowercase, one digit and one special character ? / ~ # ! @ $ % ^ &#38; * + | ,</string>
	<string name="signup_signup_failed">Sign-up failed</string>

</resources>
